Aranya Kishor Das

Developer | Designer | Researcher







Profile Summary

Tech enthusiast with an outstanding academic record, ability to solve problems, and the capacity to comprehend and test software. I seek to work as a full-stack developer and as a researcher to utilize my skills.

Contact

Phone: +8801300919276

Email: aranya.akd@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://aranyaportfolio.web.app/

Work Experience

Technical Lead | 2020-2022

Crossroads Initiative

Club Mentor & Designer | 2018-2020

Gregorian Science Club

Club Co-ordinator | 2016-2018

Ideal Science and Technology Aiming Research Council (ISTARC)

Education

United International University | 2022-Present

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

- GPA: 3.3
- Member, UIU Robotics Club

St. Gregory's High School and College | 2018-2020

Higher Secondary School Graduate

Ideal School and College | 2011-2018

High School Graduate

Certifications & Honors

Champion | CSE Project Show Spring '24

United International University | DBMS Project

Champion | CSE Project Show Spring '24

United International University | DBMS Poster Presentation

Champion | Wilian's Science Fest | 2017

Will's Little Flower | Mechanical

Skills

Flutter, Dart

React JS, React Native

Tailwind CSS

Python

R Programming

JavaScript

Java

C, C++